I guess I'm not the only one that didn't even know about you, I have a tie for this man.
We appreciate your life coming after hours and we'll try to do this with this one again.
We're going to go and start an off-center.
There's everybody in here.
I hope this leads up to some discussion and obviously we'll only need you to know the future to discuss it more.
Kind of that ability to do the class meetings, you know, large things as well.
Think about your experiences.
I'm here as a team so the city's different countries are a...
So we don't have probably as much.
They don't have to do a different thing.
They have to ask if you have a DVD or a fair complex.
I'm very proud of staff.
I think that's like a lot of people can get into this.
I'm very proud of it.
I think that it's like a lot of people can get into this at first time.
You better also down on the street.
I think that's, you know, really kind of see, like, a couple of legends made.
So that was kind of a cool thing.
Some of them now, that I would like to experiment to the next thing.
And I think you should probably like start benchmarking ourselves out of the city.
I mean, do we have...
Do we have to be in part?
Do we have...
Are we doing our own practices?
That's a question, just a minute.
It's something we probably can do in mind.
We do a vision set.
And also something that I know has that it came more.
I think we should probably have a proper process all of it.
It's going to be like that.
But there are a bunch of things that we can do.
These look good.
Do you actually look at something that you're like,
Do you have a lot of personal thoughts?
Or do you have to be in part?
I mean, you have to be in part.
You know, it's just really just a jail of Jennifer.
I don't know.
I don't think we can do a lot of things.
You know, everything about the budget is awesome.
And I'm going to jail.
We have to...
There's a lot to take.
I appreciate it.
Okay, so come on, thanks.
I'm going to go to the office.
I'll go to the office.
First, thank you, the city manager.
This is a bit of a question to everybody.
30 days prior to the start of this evening.
There's a 30 days prior to the one.
We have to have a moment here.
A 15 days prior to the start of the year,
which we're going to fill that June 3rd.
I was actually trying to make it.
And the government money has to adopt a budget.
7 days prior to the end of this year,
which is one reason why we need to,
we don't need to, we don't need to,
we don't need to.
We don't need to, we don't need to,
we don't need to, we don't need to,
we don't need to, we don't need funds.
That's kind of like having 29,
many businesses.
So, revenue is all of our revenues,
and all of our expenditures occur
out of one of those 29.
So, this is the basic information about
just some details about our budget.
You know, probably know that our sales tax is not going
to be 100% in the city.
Here's the right down.
The state of the moment is 0.5%.
The county gets 1.35%.
And the city gets 3.65%.
Underneath the county,
and the city, you can see how that works down.
So, the city, 3% goes to the general fund of the 0.1 is the number of the general fund.
And that's strictly for operations.
And then 0.65 was voted out of my assistance
to do streets improvements.
And to do safety improvements.
And that the tire is 243.
And then, of course, the county has their,
their pieces that they get that 1.25%.
Uh, I'll, I will point out the point one of the fire departments.
Some of that tends to, to the city fire department.
You guys get, uh, that depends on the client's list
and then we send in voices to county to pay.
But you all will prove those expenditures.
This is just another view that you will,
I'll just grab it.
Just the same information.
And it works today.
We'll do this in the city.
So, it takes a lot of safety.
This was actually a surprise at the beginning.
So, for all the companies to,
if they get 1.5%.
We would get 36,500 in sales tax.
Of course, 30,000 would give the general fund to pay for all of our people.
Which is to fire at least parks,
cemetery, and streets, and there's quite a few departments.
And then the, the 6,500 would go to the streets safety.
Okay, the bonds.
They're in May.
We just did, we just got our May sales tax on 15.
Um, we are now at $8 million, $80,000.
And that, of course, it's $221 million in sales tax.
That is a great thing.
You can use that every day.
Yeah.
I was surprised.
It's not going to be a slide at school about it.
I think whatever we do is something we do today.
I mean, do you want to run this event as you think, okay, what kind of sales are we going to bring in?
Because they don't bring enough to take a list of things.
So we're closing this up.
I mean, you know, we're not talking about that.
It's something to keep in mind.
Carrier history.
So we've had COVID years.
And that, I think you're 21 and I think you're, I've been doing much of COVID-19.
I've never seen anything much of it.
I think we've all built and agreed.
There's been some crazy things happening.
So we hit a smart shop in, for hit this day, as smart 70 to 20.
That's when the council did some resolutions.
And that's what we have.
So we have a quick leave, we do our budget.
Because we concerned that our red goes when we cut everybody.
And we have the formula, the front cover gave that report, he said everybody has to be,
just to be able to attack and play those, we have a building that can sales tax and news tax.
So, I'm just gonna say it because I'm moving right away.
The general fund, they're normal carryover from year to year.
You average is about 1.1 million during the COVID years.
It's 2.3.
MSUA, those of these are two largest funds.
And as you may have done that.
So, MSUA, they're normal carryover.
The normal average carryover is 1.9 million.
The turn cover is essentially.
This is kind of a picture of what can happen
to a normal year, not in COVID.
You know, we have employees, we have materials.
These are expenses, and then we have revenue.
And we have a normal carryover.
Well, if a minimum of a year you get more employees,
it might affect your carryover.
Another example of a normal year, normal carryover,
is revenue gets cut for some reason.
Because we have sales tax, not to make the budget before.
So, that could affect your carryover.
There are a COVID-19 totally different happen.
None of us could project it.
I literally put the fiscal year what exactly happened.
So, we got more revenue than we got to did.
It was great.
We had our people.
We couldn't buy things because the supply chain was.
So, we had a pretty good carryover.
The next year, we got even more revenue now.
There's two plus lines.
We couldn't get, couldn't hire people.
We couldn't keep them.
And then we couldn't buy them.
So, we had a bigger carryover.
The third year, at boy 223, we got even more revenue.
From the sales tax, it just went crazy.
We hired more people in between, or we made more decisions in between.
Still couldn't get people.
And we still couldn't buy things.
But now we needed to buy more materials.
This year, we still didn't.
So, now we have this of any people versus the two.
We don't have the four.
Same revenue.
But now we're buying things and supply chain is now good.
So, now that carryover, we've got to negatively.
So, we're going.
back down in the work of one of the numbers.
Switching gears on here, we'll bring it in for a minute.
So the projected balance, this time, next year,
so June 30th of 25 is 4.8 billion.
We're budgeting to transfer in $383,000.
One of the is for MSUA, the $372 is for MSUA, the $11,695.
That is for NBRA.
They're paying back a ballroom.
They borrowed money from the R&A fund,
and they were allowed to buy the council,
and it saved them in the interest back in the day.
So there's an M&M collection of those items.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I don't throw it fast.
The current loans coming better out of the R&A fund
is the MBRA ballroom.
I tell you what fiscal year, and you have copy there,
so if you have a question, it's a call.
But I tell you the fiscal year that it was done,
and the fiscal year it's going to roll off.
So, and it's five days.
So this, the terminal, you're well aware of that.
When you approve the $1 million in an additional $1,29,
a little later this fiscal year, next year,
we have budgeted $250,000 to be transferred out of the R&A fund
into the capital of Primha, to re-election the public works.
So in total, our loans out of the R&A is $2.5 billion.
And you tell them what we started out with?
That's exactly what it's about.
When it was originally created, $6 million, $6 million, $4,000
was taken out of MBRA and put into the R&A fund
that the council has control.
So, we're down to $4.8 this time next year.
I think it's the R&A fund.
I mean, someday we're going to add another R&A fund,
or something.
Yes.
We're just being ready for those in R&A fund.
R&A funds to the R&A fund.
And we had the two new council members
that were there in the meeting.
We had a meeting where I presented some information on
what our R&A funds should actually hold.
It should hold the pre-months of our expenditures.
You had that meeting with us.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
So, that's still something that we can think about.
It should be at least three months.
Gosh, when we had no seven, I was here.
You know, seven.
We had the flood in June.
I think it's June.
Two-part of those seven.
And then the simmer for 14th of those seven,
we had the acid.
So we had two huge beam of disasters in a year or so.
So for you to respond.
Okay.
I'd like to point it out.
Go back to.
So her projected balance of theirs is 4.8 billion.
We had a meeting about this back in January.
And I take the notes and back then he said,
we were anticipating we had about 4.6 million by June.
So that's even higher than what we projected six months ago.
Well, I'm seeing that.
Yeah.
Well, that's at 20.
Was that number I think?
Was that just said, as of June 2020, 24, we would have 4.6 million more.
Okay.
So again, this is next year, 25, 4.8 million more.
And we're taking it out too.
So it's jumping up a little bit.
Yeah, it's just good.
Yeah.
This is something I don't include in this.
So again, MSU-A and the general fund are our two largest funds, like R.
Here's just some general large revenues in each fund.
The total revenue projected for MSU-A next year is 31 million.
And these are some of the big ones.
So of course, the electric, electric, that is what makes us a different organization than anything.
If we didn't have a electric, we'd be different.
I remember I was here, and I can't have a new council member like,
We need to settle, are you telling me, I like that?
He didn't understand what this is, what I like the best.
And again, we would have to provide water, wastewater, and solid waste, if we can't waste.
But those are the projected revenues for those.
Again, I know we just approved the will down to the rate study and some waste is upside down.
We pay more to get rid of it than the charge to take it.
By say, statute, at least with water and wastewater, I know for sure you have to cover with your thoughts.
I don't know what that's all about.
To know fund, projected to bring in $12.8 million, the tax revenue category, the sales tax is the biggest account number in that category.
It's like $1.5 million.
There's a transfer in from MSU-A of $2 million, and then a transfer in, we're projecting a transfer in for the capital credit.
Capital credit fund at $5.27.
To make it bad.
We're struggling with you.
So don't worry, transfer between all these funds, I'm just showing you four funds.
But in MSU-A is going to transfer, again, $2 million to the general fund, $50,000 to the demo fund.
$500,000, $500,000, $500,000.
The city manager has to propose a budget at least $500,000 per revenue layer.
We do more than that.
We just did this to make it easy.
We just transfer $500,000.
But you do have a little bit in your street alley.
Other money is in your street alley, your gas, tax, and your vehicle tax.
General fund is transferring the $3.72, $32,000.
The ready they find that pay back for loans.
There's a utility agreement fund that they'll be transferring money to that pay some bonds for some electric apartments.
We're helping to be awarded a flood mitigation grant.
And this pre-13 is a fourth of the match for grants.
So the printed new council members, the blood donation grant, when I answer it, it is actually
to raise central rock deal 20 seconds.
So you know, there's areas of blood, it's out of the free.
Yes.
Great.
Yeah, so we know how to work, we know a lot of different things for the federal government
and the information.
We keep thinking we're getting closer and closer to the hearing, my positive view, who's out
of it.
And again, it's a pretty big deal.
It doesn't mean we're here.
Well, we've been in the same group, we've been in there running for, like, the last three
years.
I mean, is he back in more and more information?
So hopefully we'll eventually...
Any questions?
Three years.
Yeah, the first quarter, because you know, you have a year to sign up.
And we have been measured.
It's like a minute.
I feel, I know that the bill is very strong.
We're going to get it just to see a million other things.
It's something else that I think, you know, but I talked about benchmarking, you know, the
transfer, that they actually really does, is you know, it's too many.
You know, the big on-game, where she came from prior, they transferred 7,000 to 2000.
So, I mean, you know, the right players paid the transfer.
I don't know what it's going with.
Do you need dollars on holiday?
Do they really miss a penalty left for you?
Or do they have their own winter?
So, it's just, like, this set, just like this.
And then you just ran for an adult, probably that one.
So, they used it so many times.
And then, like, the person says, I see the prior there.
They're complaining, because they're not the transfer of being in the year.
Yeah.
There's a, I mean, they didn't do the big difference.
I don't know.
So, you know, it's the two main, one person here.
It's the highest risk.
Hmm.
I don't know.
Exactly.
I don't know what I mean.
You know, it's just a hard risk to really point that out.
Yeah.
That means you're like, oh.
I don't know.
Actually, I don't know.
The big connections from there and that's the report from around.
But it's actually, it's not, the part of the city.
That's really the same.
Yeah.
That's a good question.
But they maintain what we're not there.
It's because they can't mean.
They're like a whole different kind of it's not going to look real,
but you're not there.
You're actually a little bit more.
I think the budget here is not that far up.
But it's all sort of like, we're looking for it.
So, um, hopefully she can do it.
But the transfer is far less.
That's why it's easy.
So that's why I think if you get a pitch mark, you can see it clearly.
What is the one?
The wife, what I have in the past?
Yeah.
We're going to say it.
They're one, one, two, maybe less.
The wife might make that happen.
I don't know.
That's what I'm going to do.
I mean, I know that she made the comment.
The Jared Charlie.
Jared said he'd jump into this much of an empire.
But they charge for utilities there.
So like, he needs you to sum it up.
They have to make for the Christians life.
So, you know, we have this research.
They mentioned it as people from free.
I don't know.
That's why I'm going to benchmark.
Because I love data.
And I love numbers.
So it's like, man, how are they doing?
What are they doing?
Because that's unique.
Obviously, they're going to do utilities that we have.
So, I'm saying it.
It's not to say it.
I mean, I think it's perfect.
You're like your kids.
Yeah.
You're like, you know.
We're going to have to make it all over.
But most of you are still the better about mine.
All right.
That's true.
You're population's way smaller.
We have 10,000.
You guys have no documents in change.
They're there to the least over there, no.
Or they are reading something.
So, they test one.
So, I don't know about that.
Why?
I don't know.
They're like, so they test one.
So, I don't know about that.
Why?
I don't know.
But I don't know.
I don't think it was an interesting thing.
Yeah.
Well, thank you, sir.
Thank you.
All right.
So, yeah.
I know what we're going to do.
We're going to do that.
Okay.
All right.
So, the other transfers, the general funded action transfers money out.
It transfers money to the CDV.
For general operations and to support the festival market unions.
50,000 dollars for the festival.
As a sponsorship of 10,000 for the market unions.
In the RA, the main street.
There's two departments in the big street.
I mean, sorry.
Two departments in the RA, the main street.
Come.
So, for general operations for the main street, 24,700 is the proposed.
And then, the general fund is paying the other quarter of the grant match to the flood of the nation grants.
And this is the capital frequent fund.
This is where we're budgeting to send to transfer 500 to 27,000 to the general fund to balance the budget.
We're going to transfer again airport.
We're only transfers.
We do have as use.
So, the airport terminal has only used about 280,000 dollars so far.
So, we transferred 300,000.
So, now I've got transfer the next, the rest of it.
Transfer that next.
So, we budgeted this next year.
And this again is the CIP transfer.
It's going to transfer to rebuild the garage.
Potential revenue increases for this year, but you'll be seeing it.
You've already seen it.
The Cititary Performance was presented last night.
It was again.
Cool.
It was a group of the six, but many.
And then here's some other things.
So a couple of years ago,
we'll land in what they call a non-brain.
And include it all these things and others.
So hopefully we'll see something.
Because we are subsidizing a lot of these things.
So those different parts will present them.
And this is just a few.
I thought I'm a solid way of cultivating these.
I'm going to present that to you sometimes.
Probably I'm trying to get something else.
I'm trying to get something out of some other area.
It's a really good charge.
I can do it, but it's like.
Next year let's do this.
I'm going to do this.
You know, I'm going to do it three, four years.
Cross us, because if you don't.
You know, a certain number.
I'm going to be able to do it three, four years.
I'm going to do it three, four years.
I'm going to do it three, four.
I'm going to do it three, seven, seven, seven, seven.
I mean, when I said, 10 things.
That is.
That's the only way to crash.
That's why I don't need to.
into the transportation that's on the night.
I think we're going to get in the parking lot.
So, once or last time, I don't know if you could use that.
It's going to be a big deal for the next eight months.
You've been in one of my time, because it's been,
so, yeah, it's been a long time.
And if you go back there, I mean, that is,
you know, the facility is on a flat, so I think it's going to be fine.
Some large expenditures, a number of two largest funds.
MSU A is, we've budgeted 3.2 million expenditures.
Here's some of the departments that are a reasons for those expenditures.
The administration, 11 million of that is the aim of the GRA in the forward-to-perch power.
And then just here's another department.
And then the transfer out is an expenditure, so we're transferring it to 2.7 million.
And then there's a debt going to the utility agreement fund.
You're right.
It's at the GRAC sin.
it's at the GRAC sin.
It was at the GRAC sin.
No?
The GRAC is, a budgeting 12.8 million expenditures.
Even there's your, to talk,
a little bit toward departments and their expenditures.
That's a transfer out from a flood mitigation grant
Grant and then a transfer to ZDB in the industry.
Okay, we've got 1.7 million budget in.
That's in three different funds.
I don't care.
Do you have the special list on that?
I don't want you to miss this.
There's one point.
1.7 million per street repair.
It's in three different funds.
Street Valley Fund.
have to have that fund by six statute, and that's where our gas tax and G-higletechs goes.
There's also that 500,000 transport from the MSJR, and then any projected carryover.
So, 9,000 or $14,500 is a budget for a repair and extra in that fund.
On top of 500, Jennifer?
Yes, that includes the budget.
So, I have a nine, there's five other demands for the issue.
The Street State fund, again, that's the one, the Citizenship is approved, the 0.65.
So, and I've explained this in many times that I just want to explain to you that there's
another, not give this.
So, what every month you bring in about $120,000, who are the 0.65, so that goes into
the final 16.
The ballants are $8,000, so this difference sets in there, and the cantal can decide what to do with that extra.
You can repair more products, you can do some repairs on the state, and what you can pay off the
bonds, or there's no value to pay off the bonds, or later, because you may call this additional,
and it's going to roll off in 243.
So, like this year, the cantal will prove 500,000 for MC of that issue to do some kind of part of the
slower upgrade and do the turbo upgrade, and then we've had 600, and it's a change for road repair.
Well, for next year, on proposing that we have 700,000, we've spent 700,000 in the
next year, and just so you know, we keep three months of payments back, so, and because the price
of things is gone out, so we're still sectional collecting this now, which is a great problem in a way.
So, we got 2.6 million in our payments.
This is the last of it.
And they have just been with like a center of 25, so again, a little time, but that is the very last of it.
So, we have 1.7 per year, yeah.
Okay.
That's a new year.
Yeah.
What do you spend much?
But the headscaring is huge.
Yeah.
That's a good thing.
We should.
We'll have it on.
Just 100.7 to 1.7.
You like 100, can?
Yeah.
So, I mean, we'll go on and then come back and pull it forward and add it back to a couple months of
you guys about it.
And since we didn't want to go through there, so...
Barbara, you're seeing a list of the previous episodes of this last year back, so...
I think I think we've been doing a good job, obviously.
I'm telling the folks about fixing a road, everybody's...
as well, and this is just a piece of money to them all.
The problem with violence, there's no remedy for social media.
There's not.
I mean, we have a lecture, primarily, to fix a lecture in these.
There's not a speech, primarily.
So it's really a lot of work.
At this point, for me, I know the progress that they've made there,
and I'm happy with it that I have who the progress has been made.
So, we can get into a lot of strength.
We can get one to make it get done first.
We're like, being given the first, we'll probably be,
over the more than we want to be.
So they keep up with that.
And something that I'm very happy with is that we're working together.
So we go there, we do a career, we do a lot of work.
We do a lot of work, we do a lot of work.
We do a lot of work.
We're going to work with a lot of things.
But it's like, it's a long time to have a threat.
Yeah, I'm not going to cross this takes a long time.
And I think the concrete, the first last month, about the same year.
Yeah, we know that the team, that helps a little bit from these people.
We can do this in these little radicals, right?
That has a great time.
If I'm going to listen to you all the time, you know, that's a really step of me.
Isn't that quite a few of them, although it's a fine,
they're a whole part of the camp.
They're a concrete street.
So to me, the old time is new.
The mine soils were bad.
I feel like you need to be strong.
Yeah, these sheet are less.
No, no piece.
More piece.
Yeah.
I'm going to go out of the past.
They're home.
What's the point?
Yeah.
And then that's good.
I've been there for a year.
So something to do is like, oh, I can't believe that.
He's like, oh, yeah.
I'm scared.
So something, I definitely aren't.
I do think the city should get created in something.
I do think we'll buy a concrete weapon.
I do think we'll do something.
Maybe we'll buy a rock.
He's dope.
I mean, we're never going to get stuck with the car.
No.
And I mean, something is.
You don't have to fight for us.
No.
No, it's just a pain.
Take care of the city.
I mean, no.
No.
Sand's drip.
Yeah.
So some of the biggest complaints that I get are on the issue.
Like going into the business is on the issue, which is obviously.
I don't like everybody.
It's a state road.
I wish a lot of people have realized it.
Get worried about some of our clients.
Yeah.
I wish a state road to kind of take their shoulders.
And then we'll show them to our parents.
So we're going to leave them.
We can't.
Or it's a state's part.
What if the railroad track or does it stop?
That's a good question.
Are you going to start?
We're going to start.
I'm going to go over the sidewalks.
Yeah, yeah.
They said it wasn't there because track it wasn't out of the city.
I don't know.
But I think on the streets that you know, maybe,
we've got a rock or a new one.
I mean, there's something they kind of want to do something to you.
And then we show up there.
But more importantly, a lot of students.
That's what it's something.
So that's what I'm going to say called me.
Just three little points.
Do that.
Sales and use tax.
So sales tax goes to the, again, 3% of the tax.
That's 3.65 goes to the general fund.
That's 1.65 to 6.65.
They need funding.
We're proposing to budget 8.5 million.
Some history is this year.
We budget 8 million.
We're projecting to bring in 8.8 million.
We've got one left.
We've got a volume to one month.
Pre-COVID.
If you don't include the COVID increase.
Our increased success tax is usually 48.9%.
Not even more.
During COVID, it was like 1.5 million.
And one year is like 16.
It's been crazy.
But that's starting to level out a little bit.
That's what's going on.
That's lovely.
It's saying, hi.
But it's not doing this.
It's doing it more than this.
Or not even, like, our point is now that it's getting closer.
Use tax.
For next year, we'll be solely used in the capital improvement fund.
We've moved all these payments full of the general fund too.
That fund.
This year, we budgeted 900,000.
We're projecting to bring in 1.1 million.
So next year, we're projecting 1 million.
The average so that Amazon started ending use tax.
Beyond line and tax.
About 1890, this year.
And that our 10 year increase has increased.
And use tax is like this.
Like 200,000.
Now it's crazy.
Just crazy.
Okay.
So the total overall budget.
So we published with all of the budget summary.
So I'm worried about that for seven days.
It's the last page of your PowerPoint.
See it.
But it says, it shows every fund.
Or it shows the totals of every fund.
So the totals of every fund for what expenditures.
Not present.
The expenditures is 82.6 million.
Essentially.
82 million.
Yeah.
80.
That's a decrease from this.
This will be of expenditures.
So it's going to be 0.86.
Because that we had 84.1 million.
It's an extra addition.
The decrease has come for.
2 million investments in the CIP projects we've budgeted, MDRA, they had a large 350,000
dollars that we transferred to over Paris to the building, so they don't have an
next year necessarily, but they help insurance fund is a 100,000 less than just budgeted
expenses.
Community support, so the city has a whole organization including all the trust, do a lot
of community support.
We have some specific, I call them, we call them as I don't work contracts for
years, I don't want those to call them, but May's, I don't know, can't it go as close
as close as possible, which is a group of contracts, senior center, community crisis,
health and those are all of the contract.
So something I want to bring to you is Jan is here, talk about the names.
We don't look at this as we sent me a contract, we give it the worst partnership, we're
happy to have both Mayor Parker and Tyler serving who are making orders on time.
And one of the things I think we have is a tremendous working relationship with the city of
Miami, we want to be there, we want to be a resource, we want to be a good partner.
We get asked for, well, not looking at having discussions going back to right after we
have moved the contract last year.
No promises were ever made, no other mistake you're going to get anything.
You said that we're having conversations about potential to raise the amount that May's gets
from 50,000 a year to 75,000 dollars a year.
But we also understand ourselves that, we also know how all those projects and all the different
places in the city, all the increased spaces in the city, ask.
So we told you to understand if that may not be possible this year.
That money, one of the things that we want to do is we are going to create a full time position
and make to focus completely on business retention and expansion.
And what that means is this person is going to slowly work
with our existing businesses that help address any issues needs that they have, whether it be
in need for more financing, capital improvements or expansion.
We've brought up my answer to every occasion that may be.
One of these is a good BRA program you can do is if you have a business that is struggling,
you might be able to intervene earlier and keep that business going as opposed to them
shoering the doors.
And so that's sort of the BRA program does.
They also look the way to be, that person would also be responsible for collecting that.
So one of these we just completed now is a business retention and expansion survey
of a lot of all our businesses in the industry and what we're looking for is
information to be used in the recruitment process of the new business and industry.
We have a lot of questions of what is our average paid for unskilled labor,
what is the average paid for steel and administrative people,
management, professional steel people.
It takes a lot of work to track that information down.
This person would be able to working with me and be able to collect that data
and have it all in one centralized location.
In any one called, this has taken you to buy the information about how many employees are in your area.
What's the total unskilled labor?
What's the average paid for professional services in your area?
We can print all that information out of the trunk of a hat once a week.
So that's what we were doing.
We've made just committed to funding half of that project.
We've worked with servers.
And the other half would have been from the 25,000 extra we've gone from the city of Miami.
What that does is because I can't do everything.
I'm going to spread it through them both with business retention and now, working on recruitment,
working on the implementation of our economic development,
working on the action plan that we've rolled out, we've been getting available.
As well as working with the state of Oklahoma to get multiple sites.
That's still the Oklahoma Sites program.
It's right now they've got one of the program that's free to us.
But it's very time consuming.
Once we complete that process, we're going to have some site ready locations throughout the county.
But we can use the types that are in trunk and track new businesses to our area.
So that's what the purpose of that was or technically still isn't in your mode.
But we appreciate the contract, more importantly, we appreciate our relationship with the city.
We want to help this with free up the world of my time.
Quite honestly, when we create this position, to do your business recovery.
Both of them are pre-tells and why do you ask as well as to make you back to forget those rules.
Because we need all of that.
And we're also working heavily on a housing study.
We're going to have that committee in place here, hopefully within the next few weeks.
With that committee, we're going to be interviewing firms that do a housing study for my aunt and aunt.
We've blessed that I've had conversations that you can talk about with the developers you may have recently come in.
build houses, but they need that.
We can't just say we need extra more houses,
they won't see it.
I'm going to need you to be more importantly,
company and houses you need at each level.
By having a system working with me,
handling the VRA program, allowing me to do more
improvement, and working together with me
on addressing some of these thousand issues.
That's the part that we're planning to work with.
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you for hopefully nothing else continue to maintain.
What you've already did, we know things are tied,
and we just want to know where you're part,
where you're going to be, and at any time you need us,
or anything, don't ever hesitate to ask.
You should have heard of the cost of another of the studies that you need.
Yeah, so we talked to several communities so far.
And basically the cost depends on the scale of the size of your community.
So I'll give you some examples of what the city just did.
The one in the year two to go, it was $200,000.
Broken arrow get there, it's the last year, it was $95,99,000.
The closest one to us that I've talked to was in it,
which is still bigger than VRA, it's just $40,000.
So taking a looking at the scale population size, the area of law,
we're anticipating that the cost of the cost for us
is going to be worth $30,000 to get a thorough study.
We applied the grants, you know, back at one of them, they're pretty quick.
Spoken with the R best foundation, they're taking in some funds as well.
Granted, gateway is working with housing and urban development more.
They think there's some funding there.
We believe we can get this that our goal is to get this study funded
without having to come and pay money out of the main to spot it.
In my own age, it's possible to sit in my own, or are you in our travel's borders.
If we have to get that or it would be a minimal amount.
But right now we're thinking we can get it funded through grants.
And the other thing to get probably one of those is time-wise,
most of those surveys, those communities, I mentioned,
taking anywhere from eight months to eight months.
Are there any other things that we're doing to study further?
Are there any other things that we're going to need to be done at the same time?
Because it can't just be known, they know we can be.
Now, we're working with lots of different projects.
If you've seen the economic development plan,
you know that there are a lot of teams in there.
We're also working with government relations platform.
The Chamber of Commerce is taking a lead on there by the one seat for our organization,
which will basically be allowed to operate on the lobby group,
and see the board from the Chamber of Commerce.
So we've worked a lot of UT as usual now.
to functional and safe level to get involved in maybe issues
other than the effect of our community.
Business standpoint, economic development standpoint,
education standpoint, job training, of course,
development standpoint.
We will have the ability to go and have those meetings
and the leadership to go down there.
The other things that we're working on,
besides housing, Tyler and I are working on product.
One of the things we're discussing right now is the
need for a world product.
So when I say product, what we're referring to specifically
is land, the build-on, buildings,
spec buildings, and all those kind of very work sometimes.
I know it was the base for many, many years.
The spec buildings are important because you have to have
a product available to be able to entice people
to come to your parents.
We've got land still left in the industrial department.
We're running out of bags.
We've got two sites, both about 20 acres,
left in the industrial department.
The build-on department was the one we were going to say
in the department.
The department of commerce, site training program.
It was taking us into the process.
We got the small, the final half of it.
There are people who try that in the highway.
That's got to come to the right now.
We'll get it up to the wheel.
We'll put this on that for too long.
So there's a lot of things that are in the work
but eventually we're going to need access to the work.
It doesn't need to be half to go on at all.
I have that property.
It just needs we can work with property owners and ask them
that they will allow, if they set the price,
but allow us to go out and do things like get to the base
and want the environmental testing done on those properties.
Make sure there's no hidden issues.
We want to make sure that it's clear that
if that property is available and they're willing to allow us
the market and we're going to have, where are the utilities in relation
to that piece of property and how much will it cost to get the utilities
from 0.8 to 0.8 to 0.8.
They have to have to be all the way home of the property,
but they need to be to the border.
Those are the consequences that we need to work on.
We need to have conversations with our plan and others.
Our tribal farmers, all the way to that border sections of land,
and just ask them.
We just want to be able to develop it.
We work with it.
We're not taking anything for getting a body.
It's just, can we have access?
Can we do this on your back?
And if they can, and that's just more slice of it,
we want to take a little for us to enter into the old little slice of land.
The way they're helping the city of mind, why can't we take the suggestion?
Money from hell, man, and give it to them?
I mean, I don't see power there around, man.
I don't think anything has the power.
I was like, if it was terrible, it was beyond.
And I asked, and I've got so many people have adopted all the systems, all the systems,
all the stuff like that. And they have those. It wasn't just a piece of the design.
It was a try to pursue a test for it.
And then we talked to him after, and they came and told him what my experience of what he was trying to do
and I was like, I'm like, what's this? I didn't know what this is.
And I was like, oh, I was like, I don't know what this is.
So I was like, I didn't know what this is. So it was pretty critical.
But they inter, they were trying to tell each other about the higher,
some new work to our rooms, and things up and back.
Without that service, what are these people that can take to that bizarre?
It's like, if I could just add, I'm not going to speak on that.
From public land and in a few places, we've got to know more of it.
I will say this. As much as I would love to have that fun in.
I think if you decide, for example, when you want to go in a different direction from hell of it,
you're still going to need funding to make that happen.
And so I'm just, I'm just, I'm holding it that out.
I think if you need to develop your own program and it's something on your own,
or you have to find a way to bring a little band to the capital.
So I mean, even the tribe would like to help put some way with that too, I'm sure.
Okay. It's even more of this, so I don't think we're going to do that on the other side.
Does that what you're doing now? I don't know.
I don't know.
Thank you, Steve.
You've got to do that.
I don't know what it's going to do.
This has been an ongoing, ongoing problem for the last three, four years.
And the one life came from no man was pretty rude, pretty arrogant, pretty dismissive.
But the count of questions, really going answering things.
We're going to question, Kevin, could you shut up?
So then, we're not going to be a little bit off of that.
I don't know where to start.
Why are you guys laughing?
We're like, it's a happy life.
I just, I'm just, I don't know.
I just, I don't know.
I just understand that.
That was our plan.
That only that 45,000 of the opportunity
was to work where we're going to match that with our own funds
to create this new position.
It will allow me to, what's the ability to be something
plus and I've had many conversations about the need to do
to detail recruitment.
This will allow me to, what's the ability to do that?
I'll actually have to comment.
So, good question.
This will allow us, what's the flexibility.
If we could do it this year, if you still hire that position,
what does that's going to be able to come back next year, because it is.
So, it's going to be the first year we've asked
on a part of the end of the whole country.
But I just want to highlight the conversation.
We're all impressed that they're back.
And you're right.
Quickly.
I know.
I actually agree with that.
So, it makes, and it's already, well,
I'm going to present you guys going to follow him back soon.
But our plan, the book, which is, if you're going to hear,
make, are to do, is that, that may fully hunt the program,
or this person, or to use.
The recent two years is important.
It is, we weren't sure.
Obviously, we, we understand that at the moment,
climate is less as any climate.
So, we weren't sure if we were going to be able to get that extra 25,
but I was going to be, being committed to funding
after two years.
But one of the side benefits of the yard program is that,
because of that contact, that regular contact,
with all of our companies,
it's going to pay all long-term in our plumbers of efforts.
So, as we continue to fund raise,
and that's what we continue to come in.
You know, that long-term, that fund raising effort,
as well as the action of funding from the city,
will fund that new fall.
But for two, four years, we're committed.
Assuming the board votes to do that,
that's not the length, that we need to commit one way or the other.
We're going to go bigger, go home.
So, if we wanted to do this,
and we truly believe this is an important program,
and we have to ask the students again.
We have to say, we're willing to hold the dice and say,
this is going to work if, in two years,
we start to see that increase in funding,
through our fundraising campaign,
and we're able to see the increase in our funding.
I think, in two years, we may not be here,
so I had to commit to that.
That was comfortable on that.
But I think that with definitely,
we may have to make another council work,
and that's what we're going to do here.
We're going to need your example on board,
or say, the progress there.
I'm not sure,
but the captain of the city,
you've got to make that we can do this year
and get a drink at the end.
But for my opinion,
I don't know if anybody else has anything on that.
Are there many things that you've started?
Or are there many things that you've started?
Is that really, really,
many times?
Is that really, really long?
You have pretty much there.
So, I know what's happening.
Yeah, I'm leaving now.
But that's okay.
It's okay.
It's like being here for the last night.
The only way we can say involvement
is reportable in the city.
We have to be present in theaters as much as we can.
A lot of times,
we can only be submitting.
That doesn't show up.
It's like a lady.
I'm sorry.
We hope that we can achieve the other relationship with all of this.
Hey, Joe, can you back up the whole slide?
I'd like to let you point out what you think, almost slide.
So, if I think you want to point out to the board too,
we have to give me, what should we, I'll point to the comment.
Last week, we had a very, it's like that one thing.
We know the past week, we transferred 95,000 dollars,
but it'll be over here, or so I will not talk about it a little bit later on.
That we've been able to get to that meeting with them
when our problems were going to begin.
Six months, who's ever setting a seat to do it in six months.
But they like to see the budget,
we kind of basically had an awesome thing for it.
We drove them a little bit, because of me, so type, we're not going to change to 95,000.
And they see, you know, there is a point in, but they obviously saw them,
they carry over with high-end interest in the city's decision to do that.
The other thing, I think it's cool, and it's not going to be a credit.
We are health insurance, you know,
we're a question manager, one thousand dollars less.
It's pretty cool, you know, but I think they want to, so thank you, Cindy, and I understand that.
And everybody did that, so that's kind of cool.
I'm something else.
I'm going to bring it to, we will be increasing the retirement premium by 5% to our retirees
that have the city's health insurance.
So our current budget costs were health insurance,
we're going to go over a month and $6 or $84.85.
Retire insurance, we're going to bring it down to $6,000.
So we're going to increase that.
So I thought the board may be all of the retirees that you had a lot of time in the insurance,
go ahead and see if that was the cost of the city in the work, come up with your hand.
So it has a many increased in the city's 14 years.
So I just wanted to point that out.
I was going to just play call with a certain moment that the city's going to be right now.
So this is something we definitely want you to do about the community support.
The biggest number here is a 1.2 billion, and that is a whole lot of few waivers,
subsidized activities, but this is very wrong.
We actually send that to all apartments and we're like, hey, tell us what, how you, what costs
things that you provide for the area.
And of course, these are contractant and there's, the money for things like the cow and savings and things.
So we see the commission right now, and I won't put you.
Can you, you have a visit to the end?
Yes.
We can have a big number of life to see work in.
Yeah.
I did that.
So this is the question we do want to have, what do you want, I prefer those contracts.
So I'm going to need to do that.
I did with the boys at Gross Club, I know you had an 80-20 utility split, and you were
a way of 80 percent that there are utilities. Is that going to be for all outside-order
contractors? Do you want me to still do what we do?
So I'm going to give you a very backstory on this. This is what I did. I'm going to do this.
I didn't really like this at first, but it's going to be over here.
It's kind of what people accountable. So I know I can't think of it as my opportunity.
Whenever all the utilities go in there, they go out on vacation, they would open the door
and turn their kitchen out, because they were not paying for anything.
So by saying, they were not paying for 80 percent, you'd make a 20 percent.
And it's all that you would have to do. Like, watch what they're using.
You know, to be concerned, like, they're not paying.
I don't really get it. This is what I need to do.
But I need to be thought of as an opportunity to do this.
So it's just kind of an idea that you're going to see what the four stops are on.
So you don't like your kind of thing?
So that's what I'm presenting.
So everybody, like, when I get to...
That's what you want to do.
But I think, I think maybe 80, 80, 80, 80 is an extended, 80, 80, 80.
We can even get each individual situation.
Because we need something different on the community cross system in which we work with.
We need to do it.
We increase 10,000, 10,000, 10,000.
Does that want to go?
20,000.
Yeah.
The direction that the council gave during the meeting was that we were doing this much as possible.
Right.
To cover all of this.
We ended up giving that much of the money that we had for spending the money.
We wanted to take care of that because there was a need.
But as I understand, we increased there.
So, previously, there was a bunch of it in 10,000.
Yeah.
They always spent more than 10,000.
That was, they think about such huge service in the mayor like it was.
Yeah.
I was definitely going to call them huge trouble.
Just a point out to, maybe some of you think it's about 1,000,000.
That was not a friend, so that would reduce it to 11,000, if you did 80.
So, maybe this three year average is $13,400,000.
The crisis centers three year average is 24,521.
And it's worth getting 80 percent.
And this is, so they're, maybe, again, they're average is 30,400.
80 percent of that is 10,700.
So, I didn't, I don't know.
I don't know.
So, I didn't know.
Crisis centers 24,500.
80 percent of that is 19,6.
So, I rounded up to 20.
I've seen the centers 14,6.
80 percent of that is 11,7.
So, I rounded up to 12,8.
And 80 percent of that is 11,7.
Is that what you want me to do?
I'm going to present it that way, and you guys can change the noise of the mic.
OK.
So I mean, based on what I want you to say, and I think you can do this once.
Well, by the way.
Yeah.
Because they can't have something to do peace.
I like the capability of peace, because I don't like the idea of us
and I don't want somebody to waste resources.
Oh, I'm really not like the community across the center.
No.
I don't mean here, but I think it's a pleasure to present it.
But we're setting me to be right here.
And if there's other ways we need to help them, there's always other opportunities
that if they come to us to say, look, we have whatever we can always help them in another way.
We actually did it story times with those sometimes if they've got a lot of hits.
We'll go to them to take steps to them.
OK.
And I can't say what we're trying to do.
But why would they have more to do this?
Um, until we, I'm going to call it a free service.
It's not free.
But we track all of the utilities that we give away.
So the top portion of the city is like streetlights, parts and restaurants.
Parts and rent, all of our parks is $140,000.
Succ sinners.
And this, this is the last full year I had was 233.
So the Civic Center was 76,000.
Streetlights, 60,000.
Tolman, 75,000.
Then here's the utility credits for different backspot organizations.
And then this is the utility resource.
I'm feeling well.
What's going on with chamber?
Yep.
Oh, yeah.
That's a separate combination of the site.
That's the site.
So whenever you're going to be, she's going to jump in.
Thank you.
It's going to be a good solution.
The city is not a good solution.
So we're going to pass through all of the park right there.
Yes.
And then we're going to do a couple of things.
Customers are going to be there.
Because we're going to go back to the area.
You know, you don't think about it.
Do you see that bottom number?
I'm going to make it.
Right.
It's a minute.
That's a lot.
So we know what that is now.
Two.
Two right here.
Can we make it?
It's a percentage of the percent.
Yeah.
I mean, it's back again.
Whenever I happen to look at it.
They can pick it up.
I want to do it.
Just a bit.
A bit.
So more information we think you're also familiar with is the GRD and the licensing and civil
losses.
So when we have the, this is the training and how much we've spent every year.
In O7, when we have the fund, that council agreed to pay 300,000 to work.
And he is from 300,000 to the civil case and he has spent 275.
But these are all the other expenditures for the other public schools.
Time to battle.
Personal?
Four, four, four, five, eight.
Four, five, five, eight.
Just a month.
One, four, five, eight.
Four, five, eight, eight, eight, eight, eight, or all of the now.
All the way to police.
And this is legal.
And you've got legal it.
You know, put their time in it.
We're going to do that.
We're going to do the work.
Isn't that a legal base?
Yeah.
That is acceptable.
Yes.
It's everything to do with the loss.
So we may have to do a survey of the sub-sour.
And that right there.
Personal?
You're interested in the kind of weather.
How the personnel are doing that?
So this is the general funding hand.
The city.
General fund.
I tell you what the full time, part time, and your seasonal.
We don't consider seasonal part of our FTE full time and quick work.
And if you see it, we might not hold number at full time.
It's because we split people's salary sometimes.
So you can see that the general fund has 120 full time people.
And we're part time people.
MSUA has 68 people and five part time people.
The other funds that have people.
Are the MSRP program on that fellow public away this year?
CDB has 3.5 people in a part time.
Airport has 1 person.
And a 1.7 percent person.
The MDRA come one has a full time and five part time.
And then the mainstream has a half person associated with that.
So that gives us a total of 200 full time people.
17 part time people.
So we divide our formula is divide your part time by three, which gives us 207.
Again, it's not included and we currently have 18.
We have 19 to 7.
I'm sorry, I'm very happy to have a team opening track now.
Some of you may notice that you did a series of important jobs.
You're about to look at those things.
Well, that's something I want to share with you.
And if you can speak to me, you may be happy to know who you are.
If you like, don't know anything about it.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
So again, we lost two ten, but if you think about it, it was two or five.
That's the time that we go around.
We didn't have two hundred five positions.
We just, we're allowed up to two or five.
Other global budgets.
So again, what do you want to do?
Funds.
What do you want to do?
These are some of the other funds.
Funds.
The fund.
The fund itself.
You have one, three other.
Other besides.
Three other.
Trust.
Have budgets.
C.P.B.'s budget.
And then the airport's budget.
You can see new revenue.
So that's a thing.
You bring a new revenue.
You can add it to your carryover.
And then any subsidy.
So if anybody's transferred money into that.
So these are all.
What you can spend next year.
And here's your expenses.
So we're on that.
Okay, sure.
So this is a big deal.
When we first asked for everybody's budget.
This is the second seven numbers.
We asked for money to send the budget in.
We figured out what our.
Uh, estimated our revenues will be next year.
And it was really bad.
We were way under budget.
This is a very good number right here.
There's a parenthesis.
We have a much bigger parenthesis.
So we send everybody back to the drawing.
We said, here's your five year average.
That's what we call that.
Personally, our five year average is not even close to.
It's good now.
What we ask is because closely.
Good to find your average.
That's.
That's how.
And we're.
So I've been in.
And this is a general fund.
We were still.
I've been until.
I've been.
I've.
So look at this.
And again, it's on.
You're.
The.
and call on me as what we're projecting for next year.
The column beside it is the current budget.
What we're saying we're going to bring in right here.
And then these are the different,
and I've got some explanations why things went up or down.
For ready, for ready versus this year.
Down here are the expenditures.
You see every department,
least fire or sports pool.
You can see their personnel, their materials,
and their other B in the net.
I refer to that a lot.
There's also transfers.
Our students, they be bonds required.
We guarantee them with our...
initially revenues, it requires that the general fund collect the 3.6 stock. It transfers it out to
initially, initially breaks it up at the 3% that comes back here and then transfers in, and in the
0.65 goes to the fund 1.16, and it's interesting. So that's why we have a very large transfer
account. But it's really made up of the transfer CD and the NPRA insurance fetch.
So that's what I'm going to say, I think that's what we need to do differently.
So those those things can be turned into renovations? Yeah.
You know what I mean? My thought is to do the, you know, that's where I think you need to
get the benchmark out of the city's you know, I have to work for my first thing in city. I've
been on Kevin's, but animal control, these are the my parents were going to make a picture.
Now there's three of them, apart from Dr. Andrew, we had 20,000 of them on the budget.
Which doesn't matter. I love animals. My wife had her way, we would have 15,000 cats, and there would be
basically, you know, the city's grown in certain areas, exponentially. So we had to have the revenue.
One of our biggest revenues in reddish, we're setting it. We're going to use it.
That is what the amount of folks in my opinion, the generous revenues we generate.
I'm hoping to give you some help us with that, but I think there's a lot of different things we do with this village.
I just hear, but you sell it back.
I think that's what people are doing, it's written down. I think that's not the idea that we can help us with that.
Hopefully that doesn't.
We're interested in this.
Chair.
I thought we got to make a few more feedback about, you know, like, for instance, it was,
the, um, part of the, there was a call for five dollars for that.
You guys pass it on that part of your call to, you know, raise your call to the public.
So there's an excellent services.
You know, I'm going to say, hey, there's something like, is there the aim to,
I don't see it, I don't know, but the, I don't see it.
Did you mention something like the, like, the amount of money you've ever been reading at this point?
Okay, thank you.
I can't see it.
Okay, let's see.
Did you want to see the,
Yeah.
Thank you.
So, if you get that angle, it's just quite kind of like a sign to chat for us, if that budget is blown out, due to what the previous household can actually have to answer.
It used to be one angle control person that you cannot take a private.
Whatever sort of shape they're right.
And then they went to the appeal shelter, but that name on there.
So, we've learned some of the places and things like that to try to curb that get in the direction.
But a lot of these increases the blow on us, or due to things beyond staff control, is what it causes,
but now we're going to find a way back, back, back, back.
Or jewelry.
And another one makes you talk about it as a dollar, which is kind of the looting of the blow.
So look at the cost of the looting.
It's just a big party.
Oh.
And that might be another very little I think it is easy.
And you have to try to get into the limo.
But it's working together with like the mainstream programs that work together with the CDB to set up the day.
But I'll be able to watch the point of view.
And then just run whatever you can see.
Hey, we did our own trail for all of that.
The town and you can use these dogs to run with them because it makes ladies feel more protected.
I've heard it.
I've heard it's actually, they do it in other places.
And it really is taken in their place.
Oh, but it's kind of nice and tight.
I think it's a good place.
Great.
So what do you want to do?
Ah.
Talk about what?
I don't know.
It's easy.
Trainers.
And all of that.
That's what my husband does.
I don't like it.
And so.
That's what it is.
It's easy.
It's easy to talk to the dog and everybody is treated.
But that's what they need because they don't train it.
No, it's easy.
That's how they live right back where it be from.
I just think it's easy to say.
But what do you want to do?
So I'm in the kind of interesting, you know, anything about the team, I'm just a city, and I'm actually with it.
The city is very, very unique to me, capital, the city side, and I'm actually very, very, very, very heavy, and capital, you know, experience.
Because we have a big project, big things, and the substations, really, we're like, we're going to demolish them.
So we look at that kind of a challenge.
And to me, how does it look like something, which then I thought was the first and now that seems high.
That is, isn't that?
That was like, that was like, that was like, that was like, that was pretty cool.
Thank you.
People are so expensive.
I mean, here's here.
There's actually a, which doesn't worry, but it's not just because, you know, we start out,
we also did, of course, a few years ago.
It was about four years ago.
It said, we did a gigatop, that was the thing for that.
You just did this about 20 years.
So we kind of started that number in the course that I came to.
It went a little bit wrong.
I just said it.
And we have, you know, we have that, you know, it's all around that.
I'm not sure.
It's kind of that.
And then here's the model.
I'm going to present you to that.
So we're going to put this back.
Yes.
With a projection of $17,000 here.
Something to point out.
And something we can wait for.
Is we budget our carryover in our revenue.
We should be paying for your expenses with their revenues.
And whatever carryover we have that.
What that is, because it does this.
Especially the code.
It's now going back down.
You're going to do one time purchases with that carryover.
We should be on that one by these few days.
So that's that's a problem.
I'm sorry.
But I think that's something that we should probably look at.
Trying to do that.
So you're going to maybe be less than an on the carryover.
So this is a general fund.
This is MSU-8 fund.
It is good.
Today, now.
We've got 7 left over here.
Again, budget carryover's problem is kind of to show you what's going on here.
So if we could, we're not going to say new revenue.
So this is the city.
This is MSU-8.
Right here are the new revenues coming in.
So charges for sales tax and all that.
It's 9.4 million transfers in.
It's 9.5.
You remember that that sales tax is going for MSU-8.
We prefer general fund.
MSU-8, back to general fund.
So it's kind of crazy.
So it's 18.9 million.
Now we've got our expenses of 21 million.
So we're over budget, about 2.3 million.
Balancing our budget with the carryover.
That that number changes.
It's very volatile because up and down.
You're going to want to grab this like here.
So there's that 17,000.
But it's balanced.
But this should be balanced here.
Not only.
These should be one-time purchase.
So I think we did mention today, so that's just going to be an example of an issue
to balance here.
Substance to be new.
We talked about this every year.
So through the end of the year, this is the general fund.
This column here is the transverse from the general fund.
I'm sorry, fundamentally mischanted, general fund.
This is the percentage of the human shoades, revenue that is going over to general fund
for general operations.
This is the percentage of expenditures that a cover is from general fund, and then this,
sometimes more than an issue, it's transferred over this next year to be also CNP.
So it is 20% of the general funds expenditures are being paid for by other funds.
That's not probably a deal.
It's good or worse.
And then you see a couple of years.
It was about right here that we had been early in the time of 2014, it was a 38% and I believe
it was in 2015.
And then we were going back to a proper 4K, and we were going to have a hard time again, and
I have to do something, and then we had to, so we got you on camera.
CIP, education is just a piece of some of the last scrub screens.
This is general fund CIP.
You can just see what they're bringing in, again, all of these things are moved to here, but
you can see that with video, we're going to buy a new column baron, the cemetery that's
in the night money, so that was one of the ones that we kind of all had to get out of the green
on these list, and then this is capital improvement for the image today.
Well, they had it right there, but we discussed it.
So right here is like buildings at North Fire, so North Fire is getting new windows, some hang
on a renewable building, building the city center, new gym doors, the green building of the
garage, there's the 250 to rebuild the public works garage, so we're also transferring in to 50 for
the rainy day.
Everybody's been out, you know, obviously the people asked where I was driving, and what was the
period of building that so far, and if you would think, well, it's definitely been the last
four, we didn't ask where I was going to go, but it doesn't all look like a city in the city.
And here in the last 50 days, the budget is under this, and we published it in the paper.
And it has a number like, oh, the one city, general, that is one fund, it's just a general fund.
It just has a name, which special remedy that several funds added together with the one page summary.
I think that's a great idea.
We get those motor vehicles we're trying to get again, or we start to come again.
Oh, the purchasing?
No, that would be good.
Yeah, I think most of them are different than which words and words.
The whole product is in it.
We see the problem.
So, sorry about some of our opinion.
It's just time.
It's something that we should be able to do.
Sounds like good.
I'd say the place has place like GD cars.
You're going to get those.
Okay.
Out there, these here.
I think there will be some light with that.
Did anybody ask you a question?
And this is probably what you're going to see.
It's just every day because it's something.
But this will be really close to what you're going to see on the June 3rd.
Okay.
So, we came over with the idea of using the platform.
The staff who watched the current cities do this.
I know some of the things that they've made.
It's hard to follow all the different spreadsheets in everything.
So, you know, because I did an increased e-watch.
But now I think it is something similar to this.
So, we kind of thought maybe it's easy to follow.
Which I don't know.
So, I think this is what I'll present in your job.
Because I think this is what you see on the last couple of years.
And the thing is, it took my time to explain.
What did you say?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I said.
You know, I said.
Yeah.
But, you know, I said, you know, I said, I don't know.
I said, I don't know.
I didn't have any questions.
We bring this back.
The first meeting in June.
You talk about what the public has.
I've heard a bunch of it here.
So, my coach, the police.
I'm the officers.
Do we have a deal with the ship?
We have several time for the ship.
There's two of us.
Five people.
The ship is the work of the ship.
And that will set us down in the community.
By the ship.
Fire.
Minimum cities.
The ship.
We have eight times after all.
That's seven.
Two or three each.
We're trying to get over that.
But.
That's probably Lisa's, is this, is this, is this, is this, is this, is this, is this, is this, is this, is this, is this, yeah.
So it's Lisa payments for P.B. that got some carers.
They've got motor solutions, body cam, and dash cam.
All that kind of cams?
Yeah, it's the work, man.
The motor all is, the water down, and everything.
So we've got you in there.
We've done a lot of good motor all of it.
Sure, sure.
We've got all of it.
Kind of.
We've got a printer from, are the other four things?
That one's not.
But like, if you push in your hands, that one maybe, that one maybe, that one maybe.
That one's though.
That one is worse.
We have to be able to do this.
How we getting in a question, the lack of a satellite company staff is in here.
Well done.
Thank you.
to a lot of time and effort to help together.
And we can counsel and appreciate each and every one of you
and your effort. This is a great team of how to be a part of this organization
and the whole and great things come from great people.
Thank you.
And again, we appreciate you guys going back.
And the budget is working in the media.
I know that one is easy because you have people that you have to go
to do the work for you, that one and a lot of other,
but I appreciate you guys going to trim that a little bit
and give us a line of the next couple of different situations
which are for your support.
So, and you know, the Shannon's request,
we just, we kind of thought about them and we just couldn't see
give a hit or whatever we're going to ask that you've got,
but you still thought that's right.
So, we do that a little thing.
So, we do appreciate our time and effort.
And then we'll put a lot of time into this.
More so, this year, then we'll ask,
we'll go to the past and that will be great.
So, we appreciate it.
We appreciate it.
We're here for you if you need us great things.
We want to be your business.
So, we just got to become one.
Yeah?
Yeah.
So, you've been a sights on the market.
Well, you have any questions?
So, we have any, you want to bring you a call on Thursday.
I thought I'm going to get it.
I don't think that any of these are those that don't know
what I'm going to do.
We should have them.
Like what the city budget is.
Well, the city.
And I'm sure they can transfer them.
I don't think that they're accurate.
They agree with you.
They agree with you guys.
Like that.
I mean, I agree with that.
Currently, it's a change.
I thought changing.
You know, we talked about it in the pilot.
Yeah.
So, I'll make a really good call.
So, they didn't have large career oversomenals.
Like the last three years.
What?
And so, we tried to find help with the data.
And we went the right way.
It's another COVID-19.
But there are also projects.
that they did not know it could use that period before and he's not seen the budget
and that period in the last several years. So after explaining how that works, we're
at the police department project. So even though the $95,000 was cut, it can't actually get
some more to work with this. And so I also think it's one of the things that we've learned about
from the SNL. Well, it'll see key office with miles that we've been seeing just the other
there. So that's kind of one of the other ones. We're able to make some of my prayer
over in the part-time health. In case you're willing to need to live workers to come and help,
and they might be safe and not there. They're ready to go to the hospital. And so these
are there for the money they have. So we're able to mix the money that we have. We also put a large chunk
into securing products, which is kind of a less talking about it here. We're going to start
with that. We're going to start today. We're going to start seeing how that's going to be all.
And the SNL, he's going to make an addition under $95,000. We're probably going to put it there.
And so he was nervous about doing it because he felt like in your previous keybook and how this
important case it failed. But after him understanding how that works, he's excited. And I think he
should be able to do it more or more. He must be like he's getting less. He's really
utilized in more just a way to write it down.
Thank you.
I don't know if it's a couple more than I don't know if it's a couple more.
I think we can talk about it as we get budgeted at 3% increase. We can't go these. So that people
certainly will keep it in a couple of weeks. That's a coalition.
It isn't working now that we're going to go four years ago. We're having a
lot of trouble with people who have been trying their roots. So that was something that
won't be able to do that. That was just kind of a statement.
There's going to be more. We're on that thing. It's like taking away as you know in the cities that we just
get here. I have to keep it running. You know, I mean, once you're selling mine, we're going to do
that stuff. I'm not going to do it. I'm going to do it. I'm going to do it every second.
You can reach that revenue. You can keep it with our decision.
It's possible.
Can you all remain here?
You might as well have to do this around if you'd like to go over any further questions.
I'm being asked to, so I'm just going to do it again.
Thank you very much.